# **Dylan Andrés Sandí Quirós**

# **Informatic in Software Development**

San Antonio /Escazú/San José (+506) 88809408 dylan.sandi.quiros@gmail.com

#### **GOAL**

Establish and consolidate myself in a company that gives me job stability, apply my experiences and knowledge in software development, equipment maintenance, graphic design, and professional development for the good performance of the assigned functions.

#### **SKILLS**

- Knowledge of programming languages such as JavasCript, Java, Kotlin, Python and C#.
- Knowledge of computer design programs such as Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop.
- Creative thinking, teamwork.
- Knowledge in developing web pages with HTML5/CSS.
- Knowledge of web programming in .net.
- Knowledge of SQL language and development in Microsoft SQL Server 2019 and Mysql.

# **LANGUAGES**

-Spanish: Mother tongue.

-English - Level: B2 BELT English Certificate, Idioma Internacional, November 2022.

### **WORKSHOPS AND COURSES**

May 18th - June 12th,2020: Basic course of Libre Office Writer.

July 13th - August 14th, 2020: Basic course of Libre Office Calc.

August 24th - September 25th, 2020: Basic course of Libre Office Impress.

October 05th - November 06th,2020: Basic course of Libre Office Base.

July 16th.2020 - March 03st,2021: Course of IT Essentials PC Hardware and Software.

May 18th - July 25th,2021: Course Junior Achievement "Yo Emprendo Costa Rica".

#### **ACADEMIC TRAINING**

2021- 2022: English Course "Tools For Success" CINDE Idioma Internacional.

2020- 2022: Colegio Técnico Profesional de Educación Comercial y Servicios (COTEPECOS) Bachelor's Degree in Middle Education.

2020-2022: Colegio Técnico de Educación Comercial y Servicios (COTEPECOS) Medium Technician in Informatic in Software Development.

2017-2019: IEGB Pbro Yanuario Quesada Madriz. Conclusion of Basic General Education.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

October 2022-December 2022

Cooperativa de Productores de Leche Dos Pinos (internship):

-Programmer, database administrator and indicator resolution at IDEAMCASEWERE Data Analysis Software

Mars 2023-today

## Concentrix:

-Technical customer service chat specialist.